Inventory of the John Ehrlichman papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- AUDIOVISUAL FILE, Appendix B - John Ehrlichman Media Tapes, 1971-1978 (Boxes 4-17)
  - Side 1: Jaworski on RN "Kup's" (March 7); Dick Gregory/Rivera, Side 2: William Safire NET TV (March 6); Roundtable, Bella-CIA, Bill Safire on "Today" (February 28); CIA Reports, 1975 February 28, March 6-7 (Tape 159)
  - HRH (March 23-30); With Mike Wallace, and "Behind the Lines" on JE HRH (April 2); 2 sides, 1975 March 23-30, April 2 (Tape 160)
  - Side 1: Theodore White/Tom Snyder (June 18) "Tomorrow" NBC TV 1 a.m., Kevin Phillips-Jeb Magruder a.m. TV (June 17); Side 2: Jack Anderson Interview, a.m. America/ABC TV (June 18) Watergate: (June 17) Henry Kissinger Press Conference PBS:, NET TV, 1975 June 17-18 (Box 14, Tape 161)
  - Interview with Leon Jaworski, circa 1976 (Tape 162)
  - Side 1: John Ehrlichman "Today" NBC TV; (June 6-7) "Meet the Press;" Tom Snyder comment on JE/NBC & Simon & Shuster (May 24); Side 2: John Ehrlichman ABC TV (June 10), 1976 May 24, June 6-7, 10 (Tape 163)
  - John Ehrlichman, Side 1: WMCA radio; Side 2: WOR TV "Straight Talk,", 1976 June 8-9 (Tape 164)
  - John Ehrlichman, Side 1: Pia/NBC TV; Martin Gabel WOR radio, Side 2: Spiro Agnew with Buckley/Merv/Barbara Walters, 1976 June 14 (Tape 165)
  - John Ehrlichman: WHBI radio, 1976 June 15 (Tape 166)
  - John Ehrlichman, Side 1: "Kup's Show" (pt. 1) (June 27); Side 2: "Kup's Show" (pt. 2) Mike Douglas Show (June 25), 1976 June 25 and 27 (Tape 167)
  - Clark Mollenhoff ABC TV, 1976 June 30 (Tape 168)
  - JOHN EHRLICHMAN, "a.m. America", 1976 July 6-7 (Tape 169)
  - John Ehrlichman: TV news/ABC TV Good Morning America, 1976 July 27 (Tape 170)
  - William F. Buckley/Galbraith NBC TV, 1976 August 16 (Tape 171)
  - William Safire/WOR radio, 1976 August 30 (Tape 172)
  - John Ehrlichman: Phil Donahue Show/WOR TV, 1976 September 2 (Tape 173)
  - John Ehrlichman: TV capsules, 1976 September 7-8 (Tape 174)
  - Leon Jaworski: CBS FM radio, 2 sides, 1976 October 3 (Tape 175)
  - John Dean, 2 sides, 1976 October 13-15 (Tape 176)
  - Side 1: John Dean (October 21); WOR TV "Straight Talk," Side 2: Dean/Butterfield (October 20); Jaworski, a.m. TV, 1976 October 20-21 (Box 15, Tape 177)
  - John Dean (etc.), 2 sides, 1976 October 24 (Tape 178)
  - Side 1: John Dean "Merv" (November 17); Side 2: "Tapes" (October 26); JOHN EHRLICHMAN (November 10), 1976 October 26, November 10 and 17 (Tape 179)
  - Leon Jaworski, Agronsky At Large/NET, David Frost spot, 1976 November 26 (Tape 180)
  - Leon Jaworski, "Kup's Show,", 1976 December 5 (Tape 181)
  - Merv: Dean's/Sahl/Shana, 2 sides, 1977 January 5 (Tape 182)
  - "RICHARD NIXON," An Evening with Clay Felker, 1977 March 5 (Tape 183)
  - John Dean, Jeanne Parr/CBS TV, 1977 March 18 (Tape 184)
  - Richard Nixon, David Frost (on) Watergate, 2 sides, 1977 May 4 (Tape 185)
  - "RICHARD NIXON" TV Capsules:, 2 sides, 1977 May 5 (Tape 186)
  - "Richard Nixon": TV capsules, 1977 May 6-7 (Tape 187)
  - "RICHARD NIXON," Frost Interview #3 (Comments), 2 sides, 1977 May 19 (Tape 188)
  - "RICHARD NIXON" William F. Buckley/, with Reeves-Buchanan, 2 sides, 1977 May 21 (Tape 189)
  - "RICHARD NIXON"; David Frost Interview #4; 2 sides, and Jaworski Interview, 1977 May 25 (Tape 190)
  - John Mitchell/HRH-Sirica, 2 sides, 1977 June 3-8 (Box 16, Tape 191)
  - "Watergate" TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1977 June 17 (Tape 192)
  - "HRH-JM-Watergate," 2 sides, 1977 June 21-22 (Tape 193)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS," Program #1, 2 sides - Edited, 1977 September 6 (Tape 194)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS," Program #2, 2 sides - Edited, 1977 September 7 (Tape 195)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS," Program #3, 2 sides - Edited, 1977 September 8 (Tape 196)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS," Program #4, 2 sides - Edited, 1977 September 9 (Tape 197)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS," Program #5, 2 sides - Edited, 1977 September 10 (Tape 198)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS," Final Program #6, 2 sides - Edited, 1977 September 11 (Tape 199)
  - John D. Sirica (Judge), on John Ehrlichman/John Mitchell, H. R. Haldeman, 1977 October 4 (Tape 200)
  - John Ehrlichman. Parole recommendation (December); Ray Price interviews/Jack Anderson on JE (December 9), 1977 December (Tape 201)
  - Ray Price, with Tom Snyder NBC TV, 1977 December 14 (Tape 202)
  - News broadcasts relating to JE divorce, circa 1978 (Tape 203)
  - "Haldeman Book" TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1978 February 16-17 (Tape 204)
  - Charles Colson, Phil Donahue Show NBC TV, 2 sides, 1978 March 13 (Box 17, Tape 205)
  - J. E., 2 sides, 1978 April 29-30 (Tape 206)
  - ....RN Book/John Ehrlichman, TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1978 May 1-4 (Tape 207)
  - "RN-JE" TV Capsules, 2 sides, 1978 May 5-27 (Tape 208)
  - RN Book/etc. and recent, 2 sides, 1978 May 13 (Tape 209)
  - JE (July 27); Watergate (July 30), 1978 July 27 and 30 (Tape 210)
  - John Ehrlichman, Watergate Hearings/, Part Two NET and Network, 2 sides, 1978 July 30 (Tape 211)
- Incremental Materials - CLOSED (Boxes 18-137)